

Email: y.didkovskyi@gmail.com
Mobile: +38-050-382-70-56
Skype: yuryuanic

Skype: yury-uanic

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/didkovskyi GitHub: https://github.com/hichnik

FaceBook: https://www.facebook.com/iurii.didkovskyi

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hello, I'm Iurii, an experienced software developer, technologist, team leader and technical geek that enjoys working with a wide variety of programming languages, frameworks, and tools. The majority of my recent development experience has focused on the Front-end technologies, such as Angular2+ framework, though over the years I have worked with Back-End, Databases, DevOps, Project/Team Management and Cloud solutions. Projects range from small static websites and pages to enterprise line of business applications, CRM and ERP systems.

I'm a good communicator, team member, problem solver and go-getter. Meeting deadlines, organizing the workflow and prioritizing tasks are my primary objectives.

My passion is new technologies: each year I study one or more new technologies for myself. Last year it was blockchain technology (private enterprise blockchain), this year it was IoT.

Now I'm looking forward to hone my skills and be a valuable asset to the company.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Industry Knowledge: Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Object Oriented Design (OOD), Design Patterns, Software Development, Unit Testing, Agile Methodologies, Web Development, Cloud Computing

Programming languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS,

C#, Java

Frameworks: Angular2+/7, Ionic2/3, RxJS, Redux

Markup and Styling: HTML4/5, CSS2/3/4, SCSS, Less, Stylus,

Bootstrap, NgBootstrap, PrimeNG

Databases: SQL, MSSQL, MySQL, Redis

IDEs: Visual Studio 2010/2012/2017, Visual Studio Code,

Sublime Text, WebStorm, NetBeans, IntelliJ Idea

Operating Systems: Windows95/10, Windows Server 2003/1012, Windows SBS Server, Debian Linux, CentOS,

FreeBSD

Bundlers: Webpack, Gulp **Testing:** Jasmine, Karma

resting. sasimire, ikarina

Version Control: Git, BitBucket, TFS, SVN(outdated)

Continuous Integration: TravisCl, CircleCl

Cloud: Microsoft Azure

Graphics: Photoshop, GIMP, InkScape

Other: Microsoft CRM, Blockchain, Internet Of Things(IoT), Vega Data Visualization, NPM, NVM,

Postman

Soft Skills: Time Management, Project Management (Waterfall/Agile/Scrum), Problem Solving, Team

Management

EDUCATION



Enterprise Management — KROK University — Bachelor of Science 1998 — 2001



 ${\bf Computer\ and\ Information\ Systems\ Security/Information\ Assurance-National\ Aviation\ University-Bachelor`s\ degree}$

1996 - 1997



Secondary school — Kyiv Business Lycee Lecos — English, Economics, Psychology, Computer Science 1987-1996

LANGUAGES

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Senior Software Engineer

Luxoft, DXC Technology company — Kyiv, Ukraine

Dec 2018 — Sep 2019



Senior Software Engineer

Citibank — Citigroup

Dec 2018 — Sep 2019

CitiBank is global investment bank with many offices worldwide.

Key responsibilities were to provide high-quality Front-end/Backend code that matches clients business needs

Briefly about the project:

Big Data Visualization tool with Angular FrontEnd

• Technology stack:

FrontEnd:

- Angular 6/7+
- RxJs
- Vega Data Visualizations

Backend:

- Java
- Apache Ignite



FullStack Developer / Angular2+ / .NET

AndersenSoft — Kyiv, Ukraine

Jan 2017 — Jun 2017

Andersen is an outsourcing company with more than 500 employees in many offices worldwide. Key responsibilities were to provide high-quality Front-end/Backend code that matches clients business needs

Briefly about the project:

US Based Customer (Startup)

- Distributed international team 50+ people (5 Countries from 3 continents)
- · Direct meetings with Client
- Bleeding edge technologies

Technology stack:

- Angular2+ Front-end
- .Net/C# Backend
- Azure Cloud



Web (Angular2+) Developer Private Entrepreneur — Kyiv,

Ukraine Jun 2017 — Dec 2018

Last 2 Years I mostly concentrated on Front-end development using Angular2+, RxJS, SCSS, and Azure as cloud technology

Private Blockchain Developer for NDA

Jun 2017 — Feb 2018

Technology stack

Backend & Cloud:

- Azure cluster 3VM with Ubuntu Linux
- MS Windows on the 2nd location (On premises)
- Ubuntu Linux on the 3rd Location (On premises)
- GoLang
- OpenSource managing tools (modified)
- Solidity contracts

Front-end:

• AngularJS 1.3 (Modified open-source solution)

Software Developer (own project)

Feb 2018 - Nov 2018

Personal IoT Project

Team size: 3, Hardware engineers - 2, software developer - 1(me)

Technology Stack:

Hardware: Arduino UNO, DigiSpark, a bunch of sensors

Software: C++ like language for DigiSpark firmware, Angular7 for data

monitoring and analysis

Senior JavaScript Developer (Contractor)

PAGE

PAGE.UA LTD — Kyiv, Ukraine

Jun 2015 — Feb 2016

Page.ua provides software services in web and mobile development of any type: from landing pages to enterprise mobile applications. Have clients from Ukraine, United States of America, Israel, China, Denmark, Poland, Estonia, Turkey, Georgia.

Key responsibilities were to provide high-quality Front-end/Mobile code that matches clients business needs

Project for the ROSHEN corporation:

Task: Bug-fix Ionic corporate application - layout bug-fixing, memory consumption optimization, add JavaScript library to get invoices in .pdf format automatically.

Technology stack:

- Ionic Framework 1.3
- JavaScript
- JavaSscript PDF Generation Library
- HTML5
- CSS3 (With CSS Animations)

Worked on JavaScript project for Folk Ukraine

Project scope and description:

Develop an interactive game that will work both in mobile and desktop devices, resize depending on screen size and resolution, connected to Facebook players profiles.

Team size: 5, 1 Dev.

Technology stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PixiJS with WebGL

and Canvas fallback, Facebook API, JavaScript sound library. The source code is available on GitHub (Without FB API)

https://github.com/hichnik/game2016

.NET Technical Leader

e-consulting

E-consulting — Kyiv, Ukraine

Sep 2012 — Oct 2012



Microsoft Partner Program Coordinator IntrasoftSoft — Kyiv, Ukraine

Nov 2011 — Sep 2012

Key responsibilities:

- Upgrade company IT infrastructure Servers to MS SBS Server 2008
- Establishing Partnership with Microsoft
- Open MS Dynamics department from scratch
- Development of Microsoft CRM to 1C Enterprise connector

Company profile:

- 1C: Franchising
- 1C: Enterprise 8
- 1C: Business Software Development, Support, and Distribution
- MS Dynamics CRM Implementations
- MS Dynamics Consulting



Founder & Software Developer

Makros LTD — Kyiv, Ukraine

2007 - 2012

More than 20 projects from small websites to corporate systems, based on MS SBS Server, Internet marketing solutions including Google AdWords, Yandex Direct, Search Engine Optimization

IT Manager / Support for Centerindustry

Project scope:

- Planning and implementation of corporate network based on Microsoft SBS Server
- Deploying Microsoft Active Directory
- Managing security, group policies



System Administrator & Software Developer AlfaBank (Bitek LTD) — Kyiv, Ukraine

Nov 2011 — Sep 2012

Responsibilities:

- Installation, support & maintenance of banking servers
- Implementation of Web banking solutions
- Administration of banking databases
- Different IT projects

Technology stack:

- Windows Server 2008
- MS SQL Server
- Oracle Database Server
- ASP.NET, C#
- HTML, CSS
- Crystal Reports



IT Project Manager (Management Company) DVL Holding Company — Kyiv, Ukraine

Nov 2007 — Aug 2008

Project description:

Rework of one of the largest football website in Ukraine Result: After rework, the website has grown from the 5th place to 2nd in an audience. Website's advertising income grew up to 10 times



Software Engineer / DevOps Zahalni merezhi — Kyiv, Ukraine

Feb 2007 — Nov 2007

Responsibilities:

- Further development & support of ISV solution Microsoft Dynamics CRM + VOIP telephony connector
- Solution ISV Certification in Microsoft
- Establishing the partnership with Microsoft (ISV Partner)
- Installation, support & maintenance of servers that hosts solution

Technology stack:

- Windows SBS Server
- Microsoft CRM3.0
- Visual Studio
- Microsoft SQL Server
- C# / ASP.NET
- HTML / CSS



Lead Software Engineer /Software Development department lead

TechExpert IT Company — Kyiv, Ukraine

Aug 2001 — Feb 2007

Responsibilities:

- Creation Software Development department from scratch
- Development, support, and maintenance of internal web and enterprise resources
- Development of web and enterprise clients projects
- Installation, support and maintenance Unix web servers (FreeBSD 4.3)
- Corporate Microsoft CRM 3.0 implementation, customization and support
- Development Microsoft CRM 3.0 AddOns and modules

Technology stack (key technologies):

Windows Server2003, FreeBSD, C#, ASP.NET, MSSQL, MySQL, Apache, SSI, Firewall(Ipfw/Ipchains), Waterfall Development cycle, HTML, CSS2, JavaScript, XML, XSL, XSLT, XPath, Web services, MS Project and so on...



Responsibilities:

- Planning, development, and support of the University's local network
- Organization of interaction between servers WindowsNT4.0(PDC/BDC) and KSI Linux
- University Internet connection planing and implementation
- Educational domain name registration krok.edu.ua
- Planning of security policies, rules for the storage and dissemination of internal information and access to external resources
- Creation and support of University Intra-net site and network
- E-diplomas program from the technical side (PGP, electronic signatures)



Personal Projects 2003 — O 2015

Fotoshare. info - Image hosting project

2006 — Sep 2015

Project scope and description: 2006 I've founded a completely free

solution to host image data

Technology stack:

Backend: Perl, ImageMagick, SSI **Front-end:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript

URL: http://fotoshare.info (Inactive now - only wev archive)

Makitra.net - Ukrainian social network project

2005-2013

Project scope and description: I've founded one of the first social networks

in Ukraine

Technology stack:

Backend: Perl, Mod_Perl, BML(Server side templates), MySQL

Front-end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Responsive Design

Version control: SVN Hosting: FreeBSD 4.3

URL: http://fotoshare.info (Inactive now - only wev archive)

Flip.kiev.ua — Web messenger project

2003 - 2013

Project description:

Development, support and promotion of Flip messenger

Technology stack:

Backend: Perl, C++, NoSQL, XML/XSLT **Front-end:** HTML4, CSS, JavaScript

Hosting: FreeBSD 4.3

CERTIFICATIONS



Duolingo — English Exam - 4.68/5.00

Jan 2014



Microsoft — MCP 2.0 Certified Professional MB2-868: Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Applications Oct 2012



Google — Google Certified Individual (AdWords)
Oct 2009



Microsoft — 70-282 Designing Deploying and Managing a Network Solution in Small and Medium-sized Business Aug 2007

TechExp

TechExpert — M2310 Developing Microsoft ASP.NET Web Applications Using Visual Studio .NET Apr 2005

BrainBench — CSS 2.0

Jan 2001

BrainBench — Perl Developer

Jan 2001

BrainBench — HTML 4.0

Paralimbench Nov 2000

COURSES & TRAININGS



Microsoft — M80404 Sales management in Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Dec Dec 2011



Microsoft — M80290 Marketing Automation in Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011

Dec 2011



Microsoft — M80411 Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Installation and deployment Dec 2011



Microsoft — M80408 Microsoft service scheduling in Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Dec 2011



Microsoft — M80405 Service management in Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Dec 2011



Microsoft — M80294 Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Customization and configuration

Dec 2011

Microsoft — SBS8516 Small Business Specialist

Jan 2007

TechExpert — Time Management

Jan 2005

TechExpert — Project Management

Jun 2004

TechExpert — Implementing Network Infrastructure Based on Linux-systems

Sep 2003

TechExpert — Information Security Standard ISO 17799

Aug 2003

TechExpert — Risk Analysis in Enterprise Information

Aug 2003